A Guide to the Director's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1926-1933
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Director's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries 1926-1933
The Library of Virginia
40942
15.39 cu. ft. (36 boxes)
Virginia. Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred
Historical Information
The Department of Game and Inland Fisheries was created by an act of the General Assembly passed March 11, 1916. The department was headed by the Commissioner of Fisheries and was charged with enforcing all laws enacted for the protection, propagation, and preservation of wild animals and birds, and fish in all inland waterways, and assisting in enforcing all dog and forestry laws. As part of his duties, the commissioner appointed county and city game wardens, fostered wildlife conservation, promoted educational programs, published and disseminated laws and regulations, served process for legal violations, and printed license forms. Hunting and fishing licenses were to be obtained from the county clerk of the circuit court and the fees collected put into the newly created Game Protection Fund. The monies in this fund were used to pay the salaries and expenses of the commissioner and wardens and for the study, propogation, preservation and restocking of game animals, birds and fish in the Commonwealth.
An act of the General Assembly passed March 24, 1926 created a Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries. The commission consisted of five members appointed by the governor and the chairman of the commission was to serve as the administrative head of the Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, replacing the Commissioner of Fisheries. The commissioner still appointed game wardens, subject to the approval of the commission. In 1928, the Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries was officially renamed the Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries.
Scope and Content
This collection is comprised of the administrative records of A. Willis Robertson, Director of the Department of Game and Inland Fisheries from 1926 until 1933 when Robertson resigned his post with the Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries to become a member of the U.S. House of Representatives.
The collection is arranged into three (3) series: Correspondence, 1926-1932; Financial Records, 1925-1932; and Oversize Materials, 1926-1932. Included in the collection are correspondence, reports, maps, notes, articles, financial statements and reports, and clippings related to the operation of the Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries. Topics addressed include: fish and fishing; stocking of wildlife preserves; and wildlife conservation and wildlife management.
The collection contains correspondence from members of the Izaak Walton League, and the Virginia Co-Operative Committee on Stream Pollution. Prominent correspondents include: Harry F. Byrd, H.W. Ellerson, Allan Epes, H.B. Faris, Max Fleischer, Seth Gordon, Harry F. Guggenheim, M.D. Hart, Charles O. Handley, M.B. Mount, William S. Snow, Beverley W. Stras, and Lewis W. Tyus.
Arrangement
Arranged into two series: I. Correspondence and Subject Files; and II. Oversize materials.
Contents List
- Correspondence and Subject Files (Box 1-33)
  - Correspondence, 1926 April (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1926 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1926 July (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1926 August (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1926 September (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1926 October (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1926 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1926 December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1926 Undated and orphan (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1927 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1927 February (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1927 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1927 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1927 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1927 June 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1927 June 16-30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1927 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1927 July - August (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1927 August 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1927 August 11-22 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1927 August 23-31 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1927 August undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1927 September 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1927 September 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1927 September 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1927 September undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1927 October 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1927 October 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1927 October 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1927 October (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1927 November 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1927 November 11-19 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1927 November 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1927 November undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 1-5 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 6-10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 11-15 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 16-20 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 21-27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1927 December 28-31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1927 Undated and orphan (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January 1-5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January 6-10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January 21-25 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January 26-31 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 1-5 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 6-10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 11-15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 16-20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 21-23 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 24-25 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1928 February 27-29 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 1-6 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 7-10 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 12-13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 14-15 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 16-18 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 19-20 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 20-21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 23-25 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 26-27 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1928 March 28-31 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 2-5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 6-10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 11-14 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 16-21 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 23-26 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 April 27-30 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 1-3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 4-5 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 7-10 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 11-15 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 16-18 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 19-22 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 23-25 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1928 May 26-31 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 June 1-5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 June 6-9 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1928 June 11-17 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1928 June 18-23 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1928 June 25-30 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July 2-10 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July 11-16 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July 17-21 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July 23-26 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July 27-31 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1928 August 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1928 August 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 August 21-31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 September 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1928 September 11-15 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1928 September 16-20 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1928 September 21-30 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 October 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1928 October 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1928 October 22-31 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 November 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 November 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1928 November 21-30 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1928 December 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1928 December 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1928 December 21-31 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous items (A-N), 1928 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Items (P-W), 1928 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 Undated and Orphan (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1929 January 1-8 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 January 9-16 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 January 17-21 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 January 22-27 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 January 28-31 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 February 1-9 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1929 February 10-19 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1929 February 20-28 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1929 March 1-9 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 March 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 March 21-31 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 April 1-3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 April 4-13 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 April 14-22 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1929 April 23-30 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1929 May 1-12 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 May 13-21 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 May 22-31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 June 1-10 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 June 11-20 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 June 21-30 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1929 July 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 July 11-20 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 July 21-31 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 August 1-12 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 August 13-20 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 August 21-31 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1929 September 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 September 11-20 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 September 21-30 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 October 1-20 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 October 21-31 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 November 1-2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 November 3-10 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1929 November 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1929 November 21-30 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 December 1-8 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1929 December 9-16 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1929 December 17-21 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1929 December 22-31 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 Undated and orphan (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 January 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 January 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 January 21-31 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 February 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1930 February 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1930 February 21-29 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1930 March 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 March 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 March 21-31 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 April 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 April 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 April 21-30 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 May 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 May 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 May 21-31 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 June 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 June 11-20 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 June 21-30 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 July 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 July 11-20 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 July 21-31 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 August 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1930 August 11-20 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 August 21-31 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 September 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 September 11-20 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 September 21-30 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 October 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1930 October 11-20 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 October 21-31 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 November 1-10 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 November 11-20 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1930 November 21-30 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 December 1-10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 December 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1930 December 21-31 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1930 Undated and orphan (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Research materials: Fish and Fisheries, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 January 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 January 11-20 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 January 21-31 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 February 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1931 February 11-20 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 February 21-28 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 March 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 March 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 March 21-31 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 April 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1931 April 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 April 21-30 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 May 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 May 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 May 21-31 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 June 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1931 June 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 June 21-30 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 July 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 July 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 July 21-31 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 August 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1931 August 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 August 21-31 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 September 1-10 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 September 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 September 21-30 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 October 1-10 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1931 October 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1931 October 21-31 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 November 1-10 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1931 November 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1931 November 21-30 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1931 December 1-10 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 December 11-20 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 December 21-31 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 Undated and orphan (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1932 January 1-10 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1932 January 11-20 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1932 January 21-31 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 February 1-10 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1932 February 11-20 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1932 February 21-29 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1932 March 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1932 March 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1932 March 21-31 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1932 April 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1932 April 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1932 April 21-30 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 May 1-10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1932 May 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1932 May 21-31 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1932 June 1-10 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1932 June 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1932 June 21-30 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1932 July 1-10 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 July 11-20 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1932 July 21-31 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1932 August 1-31 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 September 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1932 September 11-20 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1932 September 21-30 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1932 October 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1932 October 11-20 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1932 October 21-31 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 November 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1931 November 11-20 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1932 November 21-30 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1932 December 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1932 December 11-20 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1932 December 21-31 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1932 Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1933 January 1-31 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1933 February 1-28 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements: Game Protection Fund - Monthly Reports of Receipts, Disbursements and Balances, 1926-1927 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records and Statements, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Series II: Oversize Materials (Box 35-36)
  - A Bill: To amend and re-enact subsection (a) of section 3356 of the Code of Virginia, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - A Bill: To amend the law providing for the payment of bounties on certain predatory animals and birds, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Altered-Gravity Aerator Materials, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Annual Detail Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1929 July 1 - 1930 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Annual Detail Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1930 July 1 - 1931 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Certificate of appointment to Robertson as chairman of the Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Robertson as Delegate to 7th Annual Conference Izaak Walton League, 1929 April 11 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cooperative Statement Hunting, Trapping, Fishing License and Permit Sales for July, August and September, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Detail Statement of Receipts and Disbursements 1928 July 1 - 1929 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Detailed Statement of Field Service by Supervising Districts, 1926 July 1 - December 31 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - District Game Protection Fund Receipts Fiscal Year ending 1927 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Expenditures for Fish Refuges and Hatcheries Fiscal Year 1928 - 1931, 1931 May 21 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Game Warden Activities Year ending 1930 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Hardy, W. Wingo to Robertson, 1930 July 2 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Hunting and Angling License Sales Fiscal Year Ending 1928 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Hunting, Trapping, Fishing and Dog License Sales Fiscal Year Ending 1930 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Hunting-Trapping-Fishing License Sales Fiscal Year Ending 1930 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Itemized Statement of Dog License Sold During the Calendar Year, Amount Collected and Balance Due, 1929 December 21 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Itemized Statement of Dog License Sold During the Calendar Year, Amount Collected, and Balance Due, 1929 December 21 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - List: State Game Sanctuaries by County, 1927 March 25 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - List of State Game Sanctuaries by County, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Memorandum for the Information of A. Willis Robertson, 1932 December 3 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Mileage County by District/County, end of Fiscal Year ending 1927 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1929 August (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1929 September (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1929 October (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1929 November (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1929 December (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1930 January (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1930 September (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1930 October (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1930 November (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1930 December (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 January (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 February (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 March (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 April (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 May (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 June (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 July (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 August (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 September (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 Octover (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 November (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1931 December (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 January (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 February (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 March (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 April (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 May (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 June (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 July (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 August (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 September (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 October (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 November (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Monthly Report of Fiscal Division, 1932 December (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Proposed Budget for Each Year, 1932 July 1 - 1932 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Receipts by District, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Record of Wardens with 1 of 0 Convictions for 1930 October (1930 November added) (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Statement of Receipts, Disbursements, and Balances, 1927-1932, 1932 April 21 (Box 35, Folder 62)